I'm going to explain to you some very
simple systems you can put in place to
earn
you money whilst you do other things more
important than churning out content every
day. So when I am on social media
and I have the pleasure of making content
like
today, my sole objective of a video
is often to put someone into a lead
magnet. But it's not just a lead magnet.
It's not just, "Hey, guys,
download my free asset." I'm actually
going to push
people into an email automation where on
different days, one after
another,
they're going to receive a very helpful
email from me, and at some point,
some of those people are going to buy,
some of them won't.
In front of me right here
is one of the best
and easiest ones in which I've used.
This then nurtures someone over 30 days to
give them 30 different ways they can
improve their business.
I know a lot of people
are going to get this and think,
"Oh, but the information in there
is not even that good."
And they might sign up
anyway just to figure out how it
is I'm making sales,
and I implore you to do the
same. In this video,
don't just listen to what I'm saying.
You should have a look at what I do so you
can copy.